<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="welcome_messages">Hello, %1$s! You have %2$d new messages.</string>

    <string name="help0"><html><head></head><body><p><b>This</b></p> is the  <u>landing page</u> for all <strike>authenticated</strike>  PMs.\n <img src="http://www.example.com/image.gif" />	</body></html>
</string>
    <string name="help1"><b>This</b> is the best place to add your actions.
The <b>Inbox</b> is where all actions start off before they are processed.
Try to regularly scan the Inbox, analyzing each action and either discard it, do it or assign it
to a project and/or one or more contexts.\n
Once a project or context is assigned to an action, it will automatically be removed from the Inbox.
</string>
    <string name="help2">The <b>Project</b> perspective lists all your projects, and allows you to drill-down
into each project to view its actions. In addition to the standard adding, editing and deleting
of actions, the project view also supports rearranging actions in the order you intend to complete them.
This step is important for the Next Actions perspective.\n
For some projects it makes sense for actions to completed one after the other in strict order. For other
projects, actions can be completed in any order. This is configurable when creating or editing a project.
</string>
    <string name="help3">You may optionally assign one or more <b>contexts</b> to each of your actions.
Contexts are like tags for your actions. They can be locations, categories or whatever makes sense to you.
Shuffle comes with a few standard contexts to get you started:
<i>At home</i>, <i>At  work</i>, <i>Online</i>, <i>Errands</i>, <i>Contact</i> and <i>Read</i>. \n
Feel free to modify or delete the existing, or add your own contexts that suit your situation.\n
The context view is especially useful when you\'re intending on getting something done, and need to see what
actions are applicable to your current situation. For instance, you\'re out and about in town, so you
check your Errands context and see you need to buy an umbrella and pick up the dry cleaning on your way home.
</string>


</resources>
